you consider people citizens of Russia
вы считаете людей граждан России
responsible for this
ответственными за эту
war, you understand I, as a citizen of Russia,
войну понимаете Я как гражданин России
would say yes, but what will people
сказал бы да но что скажут обо мне люди
who also have the same position against
которые также такой же позиции против
the war as me say about me, what will they say about me that
войны что и я что они обо мне скажут что
I started the responsibility on them
я на них ответственность начала
Wait stop I understand correctly  that
Подождите стоп Я я правильно понимаю что
uh, you either have your own opinion, or
ээ у вас либо есть своё мнение Либо вы
your opinion correlates with what others will say?
своё мнение коррелирует с тем что Скажут
Well, I probably would
другие м Ну наверное хотелось бы
still like for me to have my own
всё-таки чтобы у меня было именно своё
opinion. Hello, Hello, I’m from the
мнение Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из
city of Khmelnitsky, where are you from? From the city of
города Хмельницкий Вы откуда Из города
Samara, Samara understood on the Volga Yes, this  on the
Самары Самара понял на Волге Да это на
Volga What are you talking about? I’m
Волге О чём общаетесь
looking for people living in Ukraine to just
ищу людей живущих в Украине чтобы просто
talk to find out their opinion
поговорить узнать мнение
in
во
Let’s Well, this is probably the Armed Forces that I wanted to
Давайте Ну это наверно ВС что хотел
ask a question, let’s formulate
спросить вопрос сформулируйте давайте
how do you feel about that part of the
как вы относитесь к той части населения
Russian population that is against
России которая против
the war, for me people who are against the war
войны для меня люди которые против войны
are divided into two categories: one sits  They’re
делятся на две категории одни сидят
not doing anything and others are doing something. They’re
ничего не делают а другие чтото делают
really against the war. I see
наво действительно против войны я вижу
people who are doing something in the Russian
люди которые что-то делают в Российской
Federation. I see people who are simply against
Федерации я вижу а которые просто против
the war, but they’re sitting and saying that we’re
войны но сидят и рассказывают что Мы
great. We’re against the war, but this is already the third
молодцы Мы против войны но уже третий
year of delivery, this is a good point.  I
год поставке это это хорошее замечание
agree, really, I just would like to
согласен правда я просто хотел бы
ask, no, in general, is it right to
спросить а Не ну вообще Правильно ли
expect or ask for
ожидать или просить от кого-то героизма
heroism from someone? Well, to ask to expect heroism from someone.
Ну просить ожидать от кого-то героизма
Is it right, in the sense of what kind of
Правильно ли это в смысле какого
heroism, for
героизма
Russians who are
о том чтобы россияне которые
really against the war to
действительно против войны начинали
really begin to act? But these
действительно действовать Но эти
actions  within the framework of the law of the Russian
действия в рамках закона Российской
Federation Unfortunately it will Will be
Федерации К сожалению будет Будут
considered extremism even if in
рассматриваться экстремизмом даже если в
civilized countries it will be
цивилизованных странах это будет
considered an ordinary rally in our
считаться за обычный митинг в нашей же
country, this is honestly telling me
стране это вот честно говорю мне
I can understand you Well, that is,
на я могу вас понять Да ну то есть
look uh it turns out
смотри ээ получается
uh Russia on behalf of the citizens of the Russian
ээ Россия от имени граждан Российской
Federation  kill people in Ukraine and Citizens of the
Федерации уби людей в Украине а Граждане
Russian Federation are afraid to get hit with a
Российской Федерации боятся получить
baton
дубинкой
I agree, yes it was Well, at
по Я согласен да это был Ну по крайней
least Until the twenty-second year, people
мере До двадцать второго года люди
who did not go to rallies were afraid
которые не выходили на митинги боялись
that the National Guard would beat them with sticks,
то что их росгвардия с палками побьёт
this is really quite scary, I myself
это действительно довольно стрёмно я сам
was at the rallies in the nineteenth  18 years ago
был на митингах в девятнадцатом 18 годах
When the screws in the country were not yet
Когда ещё гайки в стране не были так
tightened so tightly When the war had already
сильно закручены Когда уже война
begun, for this they don’t beat you with a stick but
началась за это не палкой бьют а в
go to prison
тюрьму сажают
Horror and yes, I agree people who are
Ужас а так да я согласен люди которые
afraid of the stick from the National Guard are weak
боятся палки от росгвардии это слабые
people, call it some kind of construct
люди это назвать это каким-то конструк
Well, a popular construct  like calling them some kind of people
Ну народным конструк типа народом
who are afraid of their
каким-то назвать которые боятся свою
power is why they kill with sticks Well, yes, it’s
власть то что палками заб Ну да это
strange, but you
странно но вы
understand with
понимаете
electric shocks they kill in Kharkov they kill in
токами убивают в Харькове убивают в
Kiev they kill I understand yes I agree
Киеве убивают я понимаю да Я соглас
Russia kills every day while these
Россия убивает каждый день пока вот эти
people are afraid that they might not beat them with sticks
люди боятся что могут их и не палками
Yes, on their behalf. So you consider
побить Да от их имени Вот вы вы считаете
people, citizens of Russia, responsible for
людей граждан России ответственными за
this
эту
war, you understand. I, as a citizen of Russia,
войну понимаете Я как гражданин России
would say yes, but what will people
сказал бы да но что скажут обо мне люди
who also have the same position against
которые также такой же позиции против
the war as me say about me, what will they say about me, that
войны что и я что они обо мне скажут что
I started the responsibility on them  pop, I
я на них ответственность начала поп я
understand correctly
правильно понимаю
that you either have your own opinion, or
что у вас либо есть своё мнение Либо вы
your opinion is correlated with what
своё мнение коррелируется с тем что
others will say. Well, I probably would still like
другие Ну наверное хотелось бы всё-таки
for me to have my own opinion about.
чтобы у меня было именно своё мнение о
That is, you would like for you to
То есть тебе хотелось бы чтобы у тебя
have your own opinion. Well, maybe I  Of course, I
было своё мнение Ну может я конечно
expressed myself incorrectly, but I meant
неправильно выразился но я имел в виду
that of course it’s cool when a
то что конечно же это круто когда у
person has his own opinion, it doesn’t depend on
человека своё мнение оно не зависит от
others, you’re laughing, I
других вы смеётесь я неправильно
probably expressed myself incorrectly, somehow it’s inconvenient, even well, to
наверное выразился как-то неудобно даже
express it correctly, let’s try to
ну выразить правильно давай попробуй
express it correctly now, well, you
выразить правильно сейчас ну вы имели в
meant to ask  uh Does my
виду хотели спросить ээ Зависит ли моё
opinion depend on
мнение от
others? Yes, I asked you about your opinion,
других Да я тебя спросил про твоё мнение
you say, I could say, but
ты говоришь я мог бы сказать но меня не
others who are also
поймут другие которые также
silent will not understand me, what did I want to say, let
молчат я что что я хотел сказать давайте
me now try to formulate it
я сейчас попробую э сформулировать
normally And initially we talked about the fact
нормально А изначально мы говорили о том
that people who  against war but at the
что люди которые против войны но при
same time they don’t act Well, in general, you
этом не действуют Ну вообще вы сказали
initially said about collective
изначально о коллективной
responsibility, I think correctly.
ответственности я правильно полагаю
Let’s. Can you ask me questions, I’m
Давайте Можете вы задавать мне вопросы я
a little confused, let me repeat
немного растерялся давайте я повторю
the question, do you think that
вопрос считаете ли вы что Граждане
Russian citizens are not residents but citizens
Российской не жители а граждане потому
because a resident may not be citizens of another
что житель может быть граждан не другой
country  Citizens of the Russian Federation
страны Граждане Российской Федерации
are responsible for Russia's war against
ответственны за войну России против
Ukraine Well, okay, let's answer
Украины Ну давай Хорошо давайте отвечу
Yes responsible. Now
Да ответственный Всё теперь
the question is. If you, for example,
вопрос Если вы например
cause damage to someone else's car with your car,
своей машиной наносите ущерб чужой
who should compensate for the damage? Well,
машине кто должен возмещать ущерб Ну
naturally, well, in general, the insurance company.
естественно Ну вообще страховая компания
But I'm the one who is to blame, not the insurance
Но я тот кто виноват не не страховая
company, but the one who  caused It’s just that
компания а тот кто нанёс Просто у него у
he may have an agreement with the insurance company.
него может быть со страховой компанией
Yes, that is, the responsibility
договор Да вот то есть ответственность
lies with who we are and he compensates for the damage.
лежит на то кто нас и он возмещает ущерб
How he will do this through the insurance
Как он это сделает через страховую
money, no one cares anymore, that’s the
бабушка деньги прине уже никого не
question:
вот вопрос
If the Citizens of the Russian
Если Граждане Российской
Federation are responsible for this war, then
Федерации ответственны за эту войну то
who should eliminate its consequences themselves
кто должен устранять её последствия сами
Citizens of the Russian
Граждане Российской
Federation and so it turns out,
Федерации а так получается смотри
Citizens of the Russian fi
Граждане Российской фи
that end this howl of the ZSU so that the ZSU comes and
что эту вой закончи зсу чтоб зсу пришло
wins and liberates
победило освободило
So, well, a good point Yes,
Так ну хорошее замечание Да
indeed, I also have a friend from Kiev,
действительно У меня тоже друг с Киева
he also asks me such questions, he says
он мне тоже такие вопросы задаёт говорит
that
то что
why should Ukrainians  to solve our
почему украинцы должны решать нашу
problem of totalitarianism, we must
проблему тоталитаризма мы сами должны
solve this ourselves I
это решать я
agree the question is coming out from Ukraine
согласен вопрос ам выходит об с Украин
I had warm relations with the Ukrainians even before the war
у меня ещ до войны с украинцами были
because I had a
тёплые отношения потому что у меня было
lot of friends we communicated and Well, how am
очень много друзей мы общались и Ну как
I a young man playing now now
я молодой человек играли сейчас сейчас
Why are you coming to  chat roulette with
Почему ты заходишь в чат рулетку с
Ukrainians you communicate
украинцами общаешься
I would like to apologize for the Russian
хотелось бы извиниться за российский
people who
народ что у
live here who support this
нас живут которые поддерживают это
bloodshed aggressive aggressive
кровопролитие агрессивную агрессивное
invasion super so look now
вторжение супер так вот ты сейчас смотри
you apologized you can still kneel there
ты извинился можешь ещё там на колени
Dasha what will it change now
встать Даше что сейчас это изменит
won’t change anything That’s the question these are all
ничего не изменит Вот вот вопрос эти все
apologies  they will be needed when it’s all
извинения они нужны будут когда всё
over when it’s all over then you
закончится когда всё закончится тогда
can say look sorry yes
можно сказать смотрите извините да
Now now yes here you are coming out to
Сейчас сейчас да вот ты выходишь
the Ukrainians telling a story guys Sorry they have
украинцам рассказ чуваки Извините у них
a rocket coming to the city Well sorry Well
ракета в город прилетает Ну извините Ну
sorry I’ll come out again tomorrow I
извините я завтра ещё раз выйду ещё раз
’ll apologize again yes like that’s the question What Look
извинюсь да типа вот вопрос В чём Смотри
what I say to all the people from the Russian
что я говорю всем людям из Российской
Federation If
Федерации Если
you are a gi, not all sorts of rallies Well, yes So why do
вы ги не митинги всякое Ну да Так зачем
you go out on chatroulette, choose
вы выходите в чатрулетке выбираете
Ukraine Choose Russia and communicate with
Украину Выбирайте Россию и общайтесь с
Russians, don’t shout directly Everything Stop the
россиянами не кричите прямо Всё Стоп
war and so on, and they start choosing
война и так дальше а начинают выбираешь
a kid there from the Krasnodar Territory,
пацанчика там с Краснодарского края
asking how much  you have a scholarship And
спрашиваешь а сколько у тебя стипендия А
how much work Yes Listen, what is
сколько работа Да Слушай а что такая
Damn, the scholarship is small Damn, we
Блин стипендия маленькая Блин у нас
seem to have such a rich country But where does
вроде такая богатая страна Да куда же
all this money go, that is, not to
эти все деньги деваются да то есть не
say directly, but to make sure that people
говоря прямо но делать так чтобы люди
start
начинали
for deputies How much money goes to war and
за замы Сколько денег уходит на войну а
could have gone  on their pensions on their salaries And
могло пойти на их пенсии на зарплаты И
so on, if out of a thousand at least
так дальше если из тысячи хотя бы у
one of the grains wakes up, it will already
одного что-то зерно проснётся это уже
be Victory, that’s all Well, in
будет Победа определённо вот и всё Ну я
general, you know, I’m trying to convince people
вообще знаете пытаюсь переубеждать людей
in real life in chat roulette, I
в реальной жизни в чат рулетке я вот
specifically just wanted to talk to you, for example
конкретно просто например с вами хотел
in real
поговорить в реально
life I have to go out to Tula and an apology to the
пере имею выходить Туле и извинения
Ukrainians is not Well, you’re telling
украинцам это не Ну вот ты мне говоришь
me this is real I’m telling you honestly I’m
мне вот реально Я тебе честно говорю мне
real I’m so much we have
реально вот я настолько столько у нас
that one died that died that was wounded such
тот погиб тот погиб тот ранен такие
news was fired upon there Yes, sorry Well,
новости там обстреляли Да ну извините Ну
sorry, sorry, sorry, this is when
извините извини извини это когда
for example, uh,
например вот
he apologized and there’s no further Yes, Oh, I’m
ээ извинился и нету дальше Да вот Ой
sorry that this happened, yes, and it’s
извините что так случилось да а оно
happening, it’s still happening This is all
случается это ещё сейчас идёт Это всё
that, for example, your dog bites your neighbor and
что например собака твоя кусает соседа а
you’re standing Oh, I’m sorry that she bites Oh, I
ты стоишь Ой извини что она кусает Ой
’m sorry that she bit again Well, like, yes,
извини что она снова укусила Ну типа да
when you already  you took her away you can yes
когда уже ты её забрал ты можешь да
Sorry it happened that way yes yes you can
Извини так получилось да да можно
say apologize an apology
говорить приносить извинения извинения
is when the fact is over And when he
это когда завершился факт А когда он
goes you need to do something to
идёт нужно что-то делать чтобы его
stop him Well yes this is a correct
остановить Ну это да Это правильное
remark, instead of
замечание мы вместо того чтобы
acting with words we say How are you
действовать словами говорим Как вы
correct how is Crimea  Well, naturally
правильно какта че Крым Ну естественно
Ukrainian Well, look now it’s
украинский Ну смотрите сейчас он
occupied. To be honest, I
оккупирован Я если честно мнение
expressed my opinion, you might not like it,
высказал оно возможно вам не понравится
but I would like Crimea to be naturally
но я бы хотел чтобы Крым естественно
transferred to Ukraine, but they didn’t do it carefully
Украине передали но делали это аккуратно
right away, just well, firstly, the authorities need to be
не сразу просто ну во-первых надо власть
changed, firstly, the authorities need to be changed, and it is
сменить во-первых нужно власть сменить и
advisable to shoot  all those who
желательно Расстрелять всех тех кто
were involved in the war and then Ukraine to
причастен к войне а потом уже Украину
Ukraine Well, how was it, for example, a
Украине Ну как это было например
scenario with Chinese regions that were
сценарий с китайскими регионами которые
transferred to other countries Yani I just
передавались другим странам Яни просто
don’t remember what it’s called, but there was also the
не помню как называется но там тоже
same experience, just wait, China,
такой же опыт был просто подожди китай
Chinese Which whales I don’t remember I just
китайские Какие кита я не помню Я просто
thought maybe  you picked up this Hong Kong
думал может вы подхватили это Гонконг
there is completely different there I’m not talking about
там совсем другое там Я не я не про
Hong Kong I’m not talking about Hong Kong I’m some other territory I
Гонконг Я какой-то другой территории я
forgot a little Well in general Crimea
немного забыл Ну в общем Крым
naturally needs to be given to Ukraine in the
естественно нужно Украине отдать в
sense of how it took so long I didn’t understand In the
смысле а как как это долго ть не понял В
sense that
смысле что
uh first to the territory of Crimea It was  it would be
ээ сначала на территорию Крыма Было бы
nice to place UN troops under the
неплохо разместить войска ООН под
control of the UN, roughly speaking, so why? For
управлением ООН грубо говоря так зачем
security, citizen security Well,
Для безопасности гражда безопасности Ну
for security. Come on. For security, what is
для безопас Давай Для безопасности чего
it that the Russian troops are going to the
что вот на российские войска уходят зат
Ukrainian howl, the Ukrainian authorities and
украински вой украинская власть и что
what will happen? Just in my
что будет понимаете Просто по моему
opinion, perhaps among the Armed Forces there may be
мнению возможно среди всу могут найтись
people who  quite fair, but
люди которые вполне справедливы но
they could
агрессивно могли бы обращаться Ну
treat the residents of the Russian
относиться к жителям Российской
Federation aggressively, and they could
Федерации и могли бы какие-то
commit some crimes, some people are capable of this,
преступления совершить некоторые люди на
some are capable of this, and it’s just necessary, of
такое способны некоторые и просто нужно
course, to protect the guilty residents of the Russian
конечно виноватых жителей Российской
Federation, but to protect them from any
Федерации но защитить от какой-либо
aggression from certain
агрессии со стороны определённых там
random people there  personalities the whole question is when the
случайных личностей всу вопрос э когда
whole army entered Kherson I yes I I heard this example
всу вошло в Херсон я да я я этот пример
Yes I agree yes how they got along
слышал Да я согласен да как там обошлись
without troops they went in normally and everything that
без войск вон нормально зашли и всё что
happened there was nothing especially there
случилось с ничего не было особенно там
were small moments what do
маленькие моменты были то что
you think yes How do you  Do you think
какие Как ты считаешь да Как ты считаешь
what percentage of people in the whole world who
Какой процент в всу людей которые что-то
somehow do something wrong can be aggressive towards the residents of the
как-то не так могут агрессивно к жителям
Russian Federation Yes? Well,
Российской Федерации Да отнестись Ну
probably small because
наверняка маленький потому что Зая и
I don’t know Zaya and Ma, I can’t just
ма я не знаю я не могу просто так
say that. Well, with one in a million, one in a
сказать Ну при один из миллиона один из
thousand, honestly not  I can say Well, it’s
тысячи честно не смогу сказать Ну мало
probably not enough, because first of all,
наверняка мало потому что во-первых в
I’m a mathematician in the army.
армии я математик Мало - это
Few is how many, well, you want to hear the answer. Well, I
сколько ну вы хотите услышать ответ Ну я
can estimate. That’s not enough, in your opinion, this is one
могу оценка Вот мало по-твоему это один
out of 100, he’s out of a thousand, he’s out of 100,000 Well, out of, for
из 100 он из тысячи он из 100.000 Ну из
example, 10,000, maybe one  - a
например 10.000 может один какой-то
person with PTSD with some kind of syndrome
человек с птср с синдромом каким-то
after the war may want some I
после войны может захотеть какие-то
got it I got it super What do you think among the
понял Понял супер Как ты считаешь среди
police there is uh one in 10,000 who are
полицейских есть ээ один из 10.000
inadequate Yes of course yes there
неадекватных Да конечно да там на самом
actually in Russia for example there are a bunch of them among the
деле в России например таких куча среди
super super Well the question is Is it necessary  send
супер супер Ну вопрос Нужно ли ввести
UN troops to Kiev because there
войска ООН в Киев так потому что там же
is a policeman there, well, wait there, there
есть полицейский та ну подожди там там
may be some
может быть какой-то полицейский
inadequate policeman Well, you see, that’s all I wanted to
неадекватный Ну понимаете Я всё Я хотел
say about the occupied part of
именно сказать про оккупированную часть
the territory of Crimea, not Well, look, let’s do it
территории Крыма не Ну смотри давай так
as you think Where are the most inadequate
как ты считаешь Где больше неадекватных
people in  police or in the army, as far as well,
людей в полиции или в армии насколько ну
if the army Well, among the army, probably if there is
если армия Ну среди армии наверняка если
some kind of army
армия какая-нибудь
that has carried out a lot
которая провела множество
There is probably a large one Well, there is a
Там наверняка большой Ну какой-то есть
certain percentage of people with
определённый процент людей с
diseases.
заболеваниями
I understand, that is, and now, for example,
Поня то есть а сейчас например
well, look, I understand that then
ну я смотри я так понимаю что тогда
you need Well, Russian  When the army
нужно Ну Российская армия когда
is withdrawn from Crimea, it will be withdrawn
выведется из Крыма она ж выведется куда
to the territory of the Russian Federation. Well, it would
на территорию Российской Федерации Ну
be good and back to the
хорошо было бы да и обратно на
territory of the Russian Federation, but I
территорию Российской Федерации да то я
understand correctly that it is necessary to
правильно понимаю что нужно на
bring UN troops to the territory of the Russian Federation.
территорию Российской Федерации вести
Well, you are asking a good tricky question,
Ну вы хороший каверзный вопрос задаёте я
well, look, there really is such a number  people
ну смотри реально такое количество людей
with SCI And so on, especially the losers.
с ТСМ И так дальше тем более проигравших
Yes, they will end up on the territory of the Russian Federation. And how can they treat
Федерации Да и как они могут относиться
those who were against the war, and so on?
к тем кто были против войны и так дальше
Maybe then, well, with the withdrawal of
Может тогда ну нужно с выводом
Russian troops from Crimea, it is necessary to send
российских войск из Крыма вводить войска
UN troops to Russia Well, logically, he is not doing
ООН в Россию Ну логично он занимается не
external
внешними
Well, conflicts in the country somewhere And
Ну конфликтами в стране там где-либо А
between countries So why, well, Crimea is
между странами Так а зачем ну Крым - это
Ukraine, Russian troops came out of conflict
Украина российские войска вышли конфликт
I agree, yes Crimea is Ukraine, but there
Я согласен да Крым Украина но там же
were also Russian troops there, Russian
были и российские войска там российский
federation Well, residents of the Russian Federation,
федера Ну жители Российской Федерации
some conflicts may arise
могут какие-то конфликты возникать
Look  what residents of the Russian residents of the
Смотри какие жители российской жители
Russian Federation are escaping through this
Российской Федерации убегают через это
through the Crimean bridge along with the Russian
через Крымский мост вместе с российской
army will still escape You understand,
армией всё все же убегут Вы же понимаете
not everyone can not everyone will escape Yes, whoever does not
не все смогут не все убегут Да кто не
escape will already be judged there for Well,
убежит того уже будут там судить за Ну в
what’s the problem a e Well, look, there is
чём проблема а е Ну ну и смотри есть
if if a person from Siberia came to the
если если человек из Сибири приехал в
occupied Crimea and lives there he
оккупированный Крым и живёт Там он
violated Ukrainian legislation Well,
нарушил украинское законодательство Ну
yes, of course, but surely such people will leave And I
да конечно но наверняка такие уедут А я
had of course they will leave, such people will probably leave,
имел конечно уедут такие наверняка уедут
they will not stay, that’s all Well, that’s
они не будут оставаться это да всё Ну и
all, everyone who came in large numbers
всё вот все кто понаехали реально это
will actually storm the ferries  Yes, it
будут штурмовать паромы будут Это короче
will be a short spectacle, yes And those who lived in Crimea
зрелище будет да А те кто жили в Крыму
Yes, under Ukraine, they were simply forced to
Да при Украине просто вынужденно
receive Russian passports Yes,
получили российские паспорта Да потому
because, well, it’s normal to exist there differently, they
что ну по-другому существовать там
will transfer back well, they still
нормально перейдут назад ну гражданство
have Ukrainian citizenship, and all those who
Украины у них осталось же и всё те кто
collaborated with the occupation army Yes
сотрудничал с оккупационной армией Да
they will too  to run away because they will
будут тоже убегать потому что они будут
receive a prison sentence there, one thing is
получать там тюремный срок одно вот если
if all these migrants are transferred
если все вот эти переселенцы перет
back to Russia and who
обратно в Россию а кого же судить
will have to be judged who will come to judge if everyone
придётся кого же прид судить если все
who was an immigrant from Russia to Crimea
кто был переселенцем из России в Крым
who will have to be judged Look, they
кого же судить придётся Вот смотри они
all run away Yes So  Then the UN creates an
все убегают Да Значит дальше ООН создаёт
international tribunal and Russia
международный трибунал так и Россия
issues it according to the list, by rank first, then first
выдаёт по списку вот по рангу сначала то
Aksyonov, then these, and so on until
сначала Аксёнов потом эти и так до
each of these migrants who
каждого этого переселенца который
came to Crimea and supported the
приезжал в Крым и поддерживал
occupation power, that’s
оккупационную власть вот и
all, that is, Russia, for example, and having signed
всё то есть Россия например да подписав
a surrender T Yeah, there is a Russian citizen there
капитуляцией Т Ага есть там гражданин
Federation now lives in
Российской Федерации сейчас проживает в
Novosibirsk Yes, he escaped from Crimea, he was
Новосибирске Да убежал из Крыма был
noticed in such and such cases, everyone
замечен в таких-то таких-то делах всё
brings him to Gaga, he is put on trial, he gets a
его привозят в Гагу судят получает
sentence Well, in general, I understand your idea
срок Ну в целом я вашу мысль
[music]
[музыка]
The question is very simple That is,
Понял Вопрос очень простой То есть
if Ukraine Yes,
если Украина Да приходит туда
everyone who collaborated comes there  with the enemy Who came
всё кто сотрудничал с врагом Кто приехал
There and so on, all these deputies Yes, the
Там и так дальше все эти депутаты Да
Russians will still be running away, just like they were
российские всё убегают будут у как с
running away from Kherson from Kherson, all those
Херсона убегали с Херсона все
who came in large numbers were blown away by the wind on the first
понаехавшие ветром сдуло в первый же
day and that’s it Wait, seriously, come to Kherson
день и всё Подождите а серьёзно в Херсон
from Russia Well, yes, there
из России приезжать Ну да Там
Russia wait, Russia is here forever
же Россия подожди Россия здесь навсегда
was there, they sent there and the deputy still
была там посылали туда и депутата ещё
settled there and so on and so on
обосновались там и так дальше
and can I ask a little offtopic question
а Могу я задать немного офтоп вопрос
a little offtopic well I
немного что офтоп ну
know I wanted to say Do you stream now or
зна хотел сказать А вы сейчас стрими или
can I Stream every evening Can I find out
може Я каждый вечер Стрим А можно узнать
your channel I just sometimes watch chat roulette from the
ваш канал Я просто иногда чат рулетки со
Ukrainians  I’m very
стороны украинцев смотрю Мне это очень
interested in this if it’s not difficult for you,
интересно если вам не сложно конечно
of course, the VN
зараз ось ВН
axis apoc tse more and more respectfully YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through SRR to your ban and a lot more
нас через срр в твый бан и дуже багато
video I don’t show people immediately I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams for this purpose for
информация про стримы тому для того щоб
Mali operational link to write
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly at once  in the meantime, there is a video in telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
sche tezh tsikava and korisna information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we are responsible for you trimati postiyny
и мы повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
in addition, show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe H
подпишись H